[{"answer": "What do they do", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Crafts", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "About the Ottos", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I mean, the way they look.  Their hair and clothing..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Not really.  The last time I saw her was at that clinic.  That was a long time ago", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Which one", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Excuse me", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Listen to me, my friend.  Listen very carefully.  I do know what's best", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The Pied Piper of my friend. By famous Hanover cit", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "It's like a song", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No.  I mean, I remember Mrs. my friend wearing some of this stuff, but...I don't feel funny about that.  I really liked her", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's right", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "The ramp", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Very slick", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Who's Mr. my friend", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You and Mom have a lawyer", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "They work for the people we're trying to sue.  Their job is to try to minimize damages.  Our job, my friend, is to try to maximize them. You have to think of it that way. As people doing their jobs.  No good guys or bad guys.  Just our side and their side", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't want you to lie", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I used to like it here.  I used to care about what happened.  Now I think I'll sell my house and move the fuck away", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "The children", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "How fast would you say Mrs. my friend was going?  To the best of your recollection", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Sevent", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "There wasn't time", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend.  It was nice to see you again, Ally", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Say hi to my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What's going to happen to my friend", "docId": "sweethereafter.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Will the police do anything to her", "qsentId": 32}]